Gardner Family papers, 1892-1994
Congregational Library & Archives
Gardner Family papers, 1892-1994.
MS5409
Congregational Library & Archives
2.4 Cubic Feet
(3 boxes)
The Gardner family collection starts with Rev. John Gardner (1868-1954) and his wife Agnes Annie Gardner (1866-1957). They were married in 1892 and had five children together: Agnes Gardner Buttrick (1893-1990), Annie Gardner Glover (1895-1934), Evelyn Gardner (1897-1990), Gladys Gardner Jenkins (1901-1994) and Rev. John Ashworth Gardner (1904-1990). This collection contains letters, travel notes, finances, writings, wills, chrurch records, birth and marriage certificates, books, postcards and more. Additional information can be found within each series and sub-series.
Gardner-Remley, Anne
Gardner, John, Rev., 1868-1954
Gardner, Agnes Annie, 1866-1957
Gardner, John Ashworth, Rev., 1904-1990
Gardner, Dorothy Luther, 1904-1999
Jenkins, Gladys Gardner, 1901-1994
Jenkins, Richard L. (Richard Leos), 1903-1991
Gardner, Evelyn, 1897-1990
Buttrick, Agnes Gardner, 1893-1990
Buttrick, George Arthur, 1892-1980
Glover, Annie Gardner, 1895-1934
Glover, Carl A., 1891-1958
Diener, Gloria, 1902-1970
Restrictions on Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted and open to the public.
Access for Gladys Gardner Jenkins family
Part of the agreement for accepting this collection was that the descendents of Gladys Gardner Jenkins will have the ability to maintain copies for research or publication of the 3 memoirs in her series (Snippets of Memory, Pinafore Days, and Backwards and Forwards). Verification required. This information can also be found in the collection file.
Acquisition Information
Collection was donated by Anne Gardner-Remley, granddaughter of Rev. John Gardner, in January 2020. Additional material may come from other members of the family at a later date.
Biographical Note
The Gardner family collection starts with Rev. John Gardner (1868-1954) and his wife Agnes Annie Gardner (1866-1957). They were married in 1892 and had five children together: Agnes Gardner Buttrick (1893-1990), Annie Gardner Glover (1895-1934), Evelyn Gardner (1897-1990), Gladys Gardner Jenkins (1901-1994) and Rev. John Ashworth Gardner (1904-1990). The Gardner family would move from England to the United States in 1913, living in Chicago, California, New York, and Maryland. Rev. Gardner was a Congregational pastor in the various locations his family lived, Evelyn Gardner was the Dean of women at Grinnell College and taught in a variety of schools, Gladys Gardner Jenkins was a writer and radio host, and Rev. John Ashworth Gardner was a presbyterian minister. Other people represented in the collection include Rev. John Ashworth Gardner's wife Dorothy Luther Gardner (1904-1999), Gladys Gardner Jenkins husband, the child psychiatrist Richard Jenkins (1903-1991), Agnes Gardner Buttricks husband, minister Rev. George Buttrick (1892-1980), Annie Gardner Glover's husband, minister and author Rev. Carl A. Glover (1891-1958) and educator and author Gloria Diener (1902-1970), Rev. Carl A. Glover's second wife.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records from various members of the Gardner Family and includes letters, travel notes, finances, writings, wills, chrurch records, birth and marriage certificates, books, postcards and more. Additional information can be found within each series and sub-series. This collection covers information from Rev. John Gardner, Agnes Baker Gardner, Rev. John Ashworth Gardner, Dorothy Luther Gardner, Gladys Gardner Jenkins, Richard Jenkins, Evelyn Gardner, Agnes Gardner Buttrick, Rev. George Buttrick, Annie Gardner Glover, Rev. Carl A. Glover and Gloria Diener.
Arrangement
This collection has been organized into nine series listed below. Within each series, records have been arranged chronologically.
Series 1: Records of both John and Agnes Gardner, 1892-1957
Series 2: Records of John Gardner, 1894-1954, 1985
Subseries 1: Religious, 1894-1952, 1985
Subseries 2: Personal, 1895-1954
Series 3: Records of Evelyn Gardner, 1898-1991
Series 4: Records of John Ashworth Gardner and Dorothy Luther Gardner, 1904-1990
Series 5: Records of Gladys Gardner Jenkins and Richard Jenkins, 1917, 1931, 1954-1994
Series 6: Records of Agnes Annie Gardner, 1918-1958
Series 7: Records of Agnes Gardner Buttrick and Rev. George Buttrick, 1924-1993
Series 8: Records of Annie (Nan) Gardner Glover, Rev. Carl A. Glover and Gloria Diener Glover, 1934-1943, 1969-1970
Series 9: Unattributed records, undated
Separated Materials
The collection originally included various genealogical information compiled after the timeframe of the collection. This information does not fit with the actual collection but was kept for future users in the collection file. If you want to view these documents, please ask the staff and they will be happy to provide them.
Related Materials
Thirteen items related to John Ashworth Gardner were sent to the Presbyerian Church of the United States of America in August of 2017. A list of each individual item is available in the collection file and can be viewed by asking the archivist.
Correspondence.; Letters.; Travel writing.; Sermons.; Obituaries.; Education, Higher.; Church records and registers.; Marriage records.; Photographs.; Gardner-Remley, Anne; Gardner, John, Rev., 1868-1954; Gardner, Agnes Annie, 1866-1957; Gardner, John Ashworth, Rev., 1904-1990; Gardner, Dorothy Luther, 1904-1999; Jenkins, Gladys Gardner, 1901-1994; Jenkins, Richard L. (Richard Leos), 1903-1991; Gardner, Evelyn, 1897-1990; Buttrick, Agnes Gardner, 1893-1990; Buttrick, George Arthur, 1892-1980; Glover, Annie Gardner, 1895-1934; Glover, Carl A., 1891-1958; Diener, Gloria, 1902-1970
- Records of both Rev. John and Agnes Annie Gardner, 1892 1957; 1892-1957; 9 Folders
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains records of both John and Agnes Gardner together, including a marriage certificate, letters, notes on trips, disposition of their belongings and a Family Prayer Book.
  - John and Agnes Gardner's marriage certificate, 1892-12-01 1892-12-31; December 1892 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Letters from Bakers to Gardners, 1900 1957; 1900-1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Letters on birth of (Herbert) John Ashworth Gardner, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Agnes and John Gardner's account of 1932 trip (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - McCall's Magazine on Gardner's and Anniston Road, 1954-08 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Letter from Agnes and John Gardner to children, 1934 1954; 1934-1954 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Disposition of Agnes and John Gardner's belongings, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Family Prayer Book, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Letter from John Berridge to Lady Margaret Ingham, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    This letter appears to have been sent to John Gardner from an unknown sender, but this can not be confirmed. The letter is available online at https://archive.org/details/wholeworksofrevj00berruoft/page/354/mode/2up?q=madam. This version is either a draft or the letter we have is a draft. Many parts of the letter are worded diffrently while other part are identical (in comparison to the digital version).
- Records of Rev. John Gardner, 1894 1985; 1894-1954, 1985; 83 Folders
  Biographical Note
  Rev. John Gardner was born in Dalton-on-Furness, Lancashire, England on May 27th, 1868. He moved from England to the United States in 1913. He married his wife, Agnes Annie Gardner, in the town of Poole, England in 1892. They would have five children together, John Ashworth, Gladys, Evelyn, Agnes and Annie. He served as pastor at Redhill Congregational Church in Redhill, England, New England Congregational Church in Chicago, the First Congregational Church in Riverside, California, and the Garden City Community Church in Garden City, New York. He died on April 29th, 1954 in Bethesda, Maryland.
  This series contains two sub-series, one of which focuses on personal records and the other which focuses on the religious records of Rev. John Gardner.
  - Religious, 1894 1985; 1894-1952, 1985; 72 Folders
    This sub-series contains the religious records of Rev. John Gardner and includes letters, sermons, and church records.
    - John Gardner at Redhill Congregational Church in England, 1894 1985; 1894-1901, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - James Lawn letters, 1899 1952; 1899, 1922-1952 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Wordsworth - an appreciation, February 27th, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Magazine of the Central Secondary School in Hull, 1909 1912; 1909-1912 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - John Gardner's first sermon, 1910 1912; 1910-1912 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Baccalaureate Sermon to the Girton School, 1913-06-01 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - A Grand Old Man sermon, June 1, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Religious Appeal to the Modern Mind sermon series, 1914-02 1914-03; February-March 1914 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - New England Congregational Church of Chicago records, 1914 1938; 1914-1938 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - First Congregational Church of Riverside, California records, 1914 1947; 1914, 1927-1932, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - John Gardner sermon, October 24, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - John Gardner sermon, October 31, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - John Gardner sermon, May 21, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Pilgrim Contribution to America sermon, October 15, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - On 1925 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Sermons given at Garden City Community Church, 1933 1942; 1933-1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Garden City Community Church records, 1939 1949; 1939, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Communion Address, 1944-03-05 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - The Human Side of the Ministry, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Sermons and notes on love, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Sanctuary Sunday, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Evolution and Religion, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - A Lad's Dream, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - A Litany of Thanksgiving and Supplication, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Joseph of Arimathaea, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Sermon Notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Do we believe that Jesus Christ rose from the dead?, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Hebrew Poetry, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - The Story of Christianity in Africa, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - "My Son, if sinners entice thee, consent thou not", undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Manuscript on Poets and Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - The City of God, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Religion in the Home, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Religions' Bulwerk of the Home, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bringing up Children in the Nurture of the Home, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Sermons on the First Book of Samuel, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Sermons on both Book of Kings, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Lectures on the Book of Job, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Sermons on the Book of Psalms, 1930 1937; 1930-1937, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Notes and lectures on the Book of Proverbs, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Sermons on the Book of Ecclesiastes, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Sermons on the Book of Song of Songs, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Sermons on the Book of Isaiah, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Sermons on the Book of Jeremiah, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Sermons on the Book of Lamentations, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Sermons on the Book of Ezekiel, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Sermons on the Book of Daniel, 1941, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Sermons on the Book of Hosea, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Sermons on the Book of Joel, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Sermons on the Book of Amos, August 4, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Sermons on the Book of Jonah, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Sermons on the Book of Micah, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Sermons on the Book of Nahum, June 6, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Sermons on the Book of Habakkuk, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Sermons on the Book of Zepheniah, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Sermons on the Book of Haggai, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Sermons on the Book of Zachariah, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Sermons on the Book of Malachi, May 11, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Sermons on the Gospel of Matthew, 1932 1943; 1932-1943, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Sermons on the Gospel of Mark, 1933 1939; 1933-1939, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Sermons on the Gospel of Luke, 1929 1943; 1929-1943, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Sermons on the Gospel of John, 1934 1942; 1934-1942, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Sermons on the Acts of the Apostle, 1937, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Sermons on the Book of Romans, 1944, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Sermons on both Books of Corinthians, 1930 1943; 1930-1943 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Sermons on the Book of Galatians, 1939, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Sermons on the Book of Ephesians, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Sermons on the Book of Philippians, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Sermons on the Book of Colossians, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Sermons on both Books of Timothy, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Sermons on the Book of Philemon, June 28-29 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Sermons on the Book of Hebrew, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Personal, 1895 1954; 1895-1954; 11 Folders
    This sub-series contains the personal records of Rev. John Gardner and includes his birth certificate, letters, travel diaries, writings, will, memorial service and outline of his books.
    - John Gardner Birth Certificate, January 25, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Letters from John Gardner to Children (1 of 2), 1912 1952; 1912-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Letters from John Gardner to Children (2 of 2), 1912 1952; 1912-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - John Gardner on first trip to the United States, June 9, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - John Gardner's travel diary, 1933 1952; 1933-1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - John Gardner's bond statement, September 29, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Writings by John Gardner, 1949, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - John Gardner memorial service, May 1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - John Gardner's Will, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Death of John Gardner, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Outline of John Gardner's books, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Records of Evelyn Gardner, 1898 1991; 1898-1991; 12 Folders
  Evelyn Gardner was born on December 16th, 1897 in England. She received a bachelor's degree from Beloit College in 1918 and a master's degree from Radcliffe College. She taught at Carleton College, Pomona College and Grinnell College. In 1933, she became the Dean of women at Grinnell College and stayed there until she retired in 1963. She was a member of Phi Beta Kappa and listed in "Who's Who of American Women and the "Directory of American Scholars". She died on January 23, 1990 in Columbus, North Carolina.
  This series contains the records of Evelyn Gardner, including birth certificate, letters, postcards, work from her time at Grinnell College and obituaries.
  Related Materials
  Grinnell College has a collection on Evelyn Gardner from her time as Dean of Women and Professor of English. The finding aid for that collection is located here: https://atom.grinnell.edu/index.php/evelyn-gardner-papers-1938-1977?sf_culture=en
  Bibliography
  "Evelyn Gardner" The Herald Journal. January 25, 1990.
  - Evelyn Gardner's birth certificate, 1898 1903; 1898, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Wayside Flowers: Illustrated Birthday Textbook, September 15, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Evelyn Gardner's report cards, 1908 1918; 1908-1918 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Evelyn Gardner's postcards, 1933 1973; 1933-1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Evelyn Gardner's photographs, 1938 1978; 1938-1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Evelyn Gardner's certificate of citizenship, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Letters to and from Evelyn Gardner, 1949 1973; 1949, 1953, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Evelyn Gardner and Grinnell College, 1960 1977; 1960-1969, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Personal effects of Evelyn Cardner, 1968 1990; 1968-1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Copy of Evelyn Gardner's Last Will and Testament, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Records related to Evelyn Gardner's estate, 1988 1991; 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Evelyn Gardner's obituaries, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Records of Rev. John Ashworth Gardner and Dorothy Luther Gardner, 1904 1990; 1904-1990; 8 Folders
  Biographical Notes
  Rev. John Ashworth Gardner was born on November 17th, 1904 in Redhill, Surrey, England. He attended Carleton College in Minnesota and received his bachelor of philosophy from University of Chicago. He would go on to receive his divinity degree from Chicago Theological Seminary. He worked at a variety of churches during his life, including Essex Community church in Chicago, Memorial Presbyterian Church in Midland, Michigan, First Presbyterian Church in Alliance, Ohio and interim minister of Tryon Presbyterian Church in Tryon, North Carolina. He met his wife, Dorothy Luther Gardner, while both attended Carlton College. They had two children together, John L. Gardner and Anne Gardner Remley. He died on August 24, 1990 in Columbus, North Carolina.
  Dorothy Luther Gardner was born on June 29, 1904 in Freeborn, Minnesota. She met her husband, John Ashworth Gardner, while both attended Carlton College. They had two children together, Anne Gardner Remley and John L. Gardner. She died on December 14, 1999.
  This series contains the records of Rev. John Ashworth and Dorothy Luther Gardner, including letters, postcards, material from Presbyterian churches where John worked, and obituaries.
  Material related to Rev. John Ashworth Gardner can also be found at the Presybterian Historical Society. You can find more information here: http://prestohost68.inmagic.com/Presto/home/home.aspx and searching for "135J"
  - Birth Certificate of John Ashworth Gardner, November 17, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Letters to Rev. John Ashworth Gardner from family, 1912 1921; 1912-1921 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - John and Dorothy Gardner's letters, 1921 1955; 1921-1922, 1944-1955 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - John and Dorothy Gardner's postcards, 1934 1948; 1934-1948 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Garden City Community Church records, 1939 1979; 1939-1954, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - John and Dorothy Gardner's Presbyterian material, 1945 1973; 1945, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bertha E.R. Strosacker Memorial Presbyterian Church history, August 1954 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Rev. John Ashworth Gardner's obituaries, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Records of Gladys Gardner Jenkins and Richard Jenkins, 1917 1994; 1917, 1931, 1954-1994; 5 Folders
  Gladys Gardner Jenkins was born in England on December 14th, 1901. She began her career teaching in Riverside, California. She would go to Chicago for graduate school where she would meet her husband Richard Jenkins. She continued to engage in teaching by writing books and speaking on the radio. She wrote "These Are Your Children" and other books on children and family. Gladys and Richard had three children, Joan, Janet and Jane. She died on July 9th, 1994.
  Richard Jenkins was born on June 3, 1903. He was a psychiatrist known for work on child psychiatry and juvenile delinquency. He taught at several schools, including the University of Illinois College of Medicine and the University of Iowa. He also worked for the Veterans Administration as a psychiatric research chief. Richard and Gladys had three children, Joan, Janet and Jane. He died on December 30th, 1991.
  This series contains records from Gladys Gardner and Richard Jenkins, including letters, notes and three books written by Gladys on her family and life.
  Wikipedia, The Free Encyclopedia, s.v. "Richard L. Jenkins," (accessed March 39, 2021), https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_L._Jenkins#cite_note-time1933-1
  - Gladys Gardner and Richard Jenkins letters and notes, 1917 1992; 1917, 1931, 1954-1992 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Snippets of Memory by Gladys Gardner Jenkins, December 25, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Gladys Gardner Jenkins memorial service, 1994-07 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Pinafore Days by Gladys Gardner Jenkins, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Backwards and Forwards by Gladys Gardner Jenkins, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Records of Agnes Annie Gardner, 1918 1958; 1918-1958; 10 Folders
  Agnes Annie Gardner was born on August 20, 1866 and died in Bethesda, Maryland on July 19th, 1957. She married her husband, Rev. John Gardner, in the town of Poole, England in 1892. She led a Bible class titled "Women of the New Testament". Agnes and John had five children together, John Ashworth, Gladys, Evelyn, Agnes and Annie.
  This series contains records related to Agnes Gardner, including letters to her children, financial information, a syllabus on "Women of the New Testament" and records related to her estate and obituary.
  - Letters from Agnes Annie Gardner to her children (1 of 5), 1918 1957; 1918-1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Letters from Agnes Annie Gardner to her children (2 of 5), 1918 1957; 1918-1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Letters from Agnes Annie Gardner to her children (3 of 5), 1918 1957; 1918-1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Letters from Agnes Annie Gardner to her children (4 of 5), 1918 1957; 1918-1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letters from Agnes Annie Gardner to her children (5 of 5), 1918 1957; 1918-1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Abridged letter from Frank Baker to Agnes Annie Gardner, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Agnes Annie Gardner and financial matters, 1952 1957; 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Agnes Annie Gardner obituary, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Agnes Annie Gardner's estate records, 1957 1958; 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Women of the New Testament - Syllabus of Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Records of Agnes Gardner Buttrick and Rev. George A. Buttrick, 1924 1993; 1924-1993; 18 Folders
  Agnes Gardner Buttrick was born on September 15, 1893 in Surrey, England. She married Rev. George Buttrick and they would have three children together, John, George (who went by Robert) and David. She died on May 28th, 1990 in Nashville, Tennessee.
  Rev. George Buttrick was born in Northumberland, England on March 23, 1892. He graduated from Victoria University of Manchester in 1915. He worked in several different churches before becoming minister of Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church in New York City. He would then work at Harvard University as preacher to the university and Plummer Professor of Christian morals until his retirement in 1960. He married Agnes Gardner and they would have three children together, John, George (who went by Robert) and David. He died on January 23, 1980 in Louisville, Kentucky.
  This series contains records related to Agnes Gardner Buttrick and Rev. George A. Buttrick, including letters, postcards, information on house hunting and records related to their children.
  Items related to George and Agnes can be found in the George Arthur Buttrick papers at Harvard Library. The link to that finding aid is: https://hollisarchives.lib.harvard.edu/repositories/4/resources/10025.
  Blumenthal, Ralph. "Rev. Dr. George Arthur Buttrick, Harvard Theologian, Dead at 87". New York Times. January 25, 1980.
  - Buttrick Family Photos, 1924 1968; 1924-1968 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Letters from Agnes Gardner Buttrick to Evelyn Gardner, 1934 1937; 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Postcards from Agnes and Rev. George A. Buttrick, 1938 1970; 1938-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - David Buttrick records, 1938 1993; 1938, 1950-1956, 1976, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Rev. George A. Buttrick's records, 1942 1980; 1942-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Buttrick Family Christmas, 1942 1981; 1942-1981 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ann and John Buttrick records, 1948 1990; 1948, 1974, 1987, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Rev. George A. Buttrick itinerary, 1951-09-13 1952-02-13; September 13, 1951 - February 13, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)